//Create array for all the questions
var questions = [];

var q1 = {
    question:"What is most effective in the following when cleaning oil?",
    correctAnswer:"Baking soda",
    choices:["Vinegar","Just with water","Boiling water","Baking soda"]
}

var q2 = {
    question:"What is most effective in the following when cleaning limescale?",
    correctAnswer:"Vinegar",
    choices:["Oil","Baking Soda","Petrol","Vinegar"]
}

var q3 = {
    question:"What material is used for making pencil today?",
    correctAnswer:"Graphite(Carbon)",
    choices:["Lead(Pb)","Soild Ink","Jet(Gagate)","Graphite(Carbon)"]
}

var q4 = {
    question:"What will be the best solution to clean up when you break a mercurial thermometer?",
    correctAnswer:"Spread some sulphur(S) on it.",
    choices:["Clean it with hot water.","Vacuum it.","Leave it alone.","Spread some sulphur(S) on it."]
}

var q5 = {
    question:"What in following is NOT one of the elements that human need?",
    correctAnswer:"Cadmium(Cd)",
    choices:["Iron(Fe)","Oxygen(O)","Magnesium(Mg)","Cadmium(Cd)"]
}

var q6 = {
    question:"What ingredient will cause muscular soreness?",
    correctAnswer:"Lactic acid(CH3CHOHCOOH)",
    choices:["Ethyl alcohol(CH3CH2OH)","Acetic acid(CH3COOH)","Formic acid(HCOOH)","Lactic acid(CH3CHOHCOOH)"]
}

var q7 = {
    question:"What kind of acid do the soft drinks contain?",
    correctAnswer:"Carbonic acid(H2CO3)",
    choices:["Citric acid(C6H8O7)","Malic acid(C4H6O5)","Sorbic acid(C6H8O2)","Carbonic acid(H2CO3)"]
}

var q8 = {
    question:"What in following is NOT a kind of painkiller?",
    correctAnswer:"Amoxicillin",
    choices:["Aspirine","Paracetamol","Morphine","Amoxicillin"]
}

var q9 = {
    question:"What acid is mostly used in car battery",
    correctAnswer:"Sulfuric acid(H2SO4)",
    choices:["Hydrochloric acid(HCl)","Nitric acid(HNO3)","Phosphoric acid(H3PO4)","Sulfuric acid(H2SO4)"]
}

var q10 = {
    question:"Which in following is the correct chemical formula of WATER?",
    correctAnswer:"H2O",
    choices:["N2O","H3O+","NO2","H2O"]
}

var q11 = {
    question:"What kind of acid exists in the stomach of human?",
    correctAnswer:"Hydrochloric acid(HCl)",
    choices:["Sulfuric acid(H2SO4)","Nitric acid(HNO3)","Phosphoric acid(H3PO4)","Hydrochloric acid(HCl)"]
}

var q12 = {
    question:"What is the material that is widely used in cables?",
    correctAnswer:"Copper(Cu)",
    choices:["Iron(Fe)","Gold(Au)","Silver(Ag)","Copper(Cu)"]
}

var q13 = {
    question:"Which in following is NOT nutrient that human need a lot relatively.",
    correctAnswer:"Organic acid",
    choices:["Carbohydrate","Fat","Vitamin","Organic acid"]
}

var q14 = {
    question:"Which in following can NOT use for sterilizing?",
    correctAnswer:"Lead dichloride(PbCl2)",
    choices:["Ethanol(CH3CH2OH)","Hydrogen peroxide(H2O2)","Hypochlorous acid(HCLO)","Lead dichloride(PbCl2)"]
}

var q15 = {
    question:"What is range of pH of acid rain?",
    correctAnswer:"<5",
    choices:["<6","<8","<7","<5"]
}

var q16 = {
    question:"Which in following is NOT greenhouse gas?",
    correctAnswer:"Nitrogen (N2)",
    choices:["Vapour(H2O)","Ozone (O3)","Carbon dioxide(CO2)","Nitrogen (N2)"]
}

var q17 = {
    question:"Why sliced apple get brown after a couple of minutes?",
    correctAnswer:"The ferrous(Fe2+) are oxidized.",
    choices:["The lutein goes out fron the inside.","It goes bad.","Because of the loss of water.","The ferrous(Fe2+) are oxidized."]
}

var q18 = {
    question:"What ingredient ripens bananas when placing bananas and tomatoes together in a plastic bag?",
    correctAnswer:"Ethylene(CH2=CH2)",
    choices:["Methane(CH4)","Ethane(CH3CH3)","Ethanal(CH3CHO)","Ethylene(CH2=CH2)"]
}

var q19 = {
    question:"What is the proportion of ethanol in medical alcohol?",
    correctAnswer:"75%",
    choices:["50%","90%","95%","75%"]
}

var q20 = {
    question:"What in following can use for cleaning rust?",
    correctAnswer:"Hydrochloric acid(HCl)",
    choices:["Water(H2O)","Concentrated sulfuric acid","Niacin(C6H5NO2)","Hydrochloric acid(HCl)"]
}

questions = [q1,q2,q3,q4,q5,q6,q7,q8,q9,q10,q11,q12,q13,q14,q15,q16,q17,q18,q19,q20]
